I'm the only one
who will love you forever.
You know that too, don't you?
I don't know if
he'll stay with me forever.
Even if he
chooses to leave me one day,
I won't blame him.
Because I love him.
Taeseok,
if you really love me,
you should let me go.
I don't want you to
ruin who you are for my sake.
You're a good person.
I got it.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
[Seoul/Incheon to Los Angeles]
These are useless now.
[Hongseok]
[Park Seonghyeon]
[Shin Yongseok] [Shin Junseop] [Ha Yosep]
[Play Me]
Yihyun!
I'm sorry.
Sorry for avoiding you.
I was afraid I'd make you lose everything.
Yihyun.
I love you.
I want to stay with you
for the rest of my life.
Oh, right.
During the casting audition,
how'd you recognize me?
Jung Yihyun?
A-Are you okay?
I missed you so much.
Before, I saw you once
at the little theater.
I was the part-time painter.
It was you?
So that wasn't a dream?
I didn't expect to
meet you again like this.
It's magical, isn't it?
Tell me about it.
Who would've thought
we'd do a musical together?
By the way, why did you
suddenly start doing musicals?
It's been my dream for years.
I only worked as an actor
because of my mom.
My dream was always to be a director.
My long-held dream has finally come true.
So why's my panic disorder getting worse?
And why's my heart in so much pain?
Is it really like my mom said,
that I'm nothing if I'm not an actor?
Yihyun.
Whether you're an actor
or a director,
no matter who you are,
I'll always love you.
[Musical: The Mermaid Prince]
Hello.
Ticket, please.
-Enjoy the show.
-Thank you.
Hello.
Two people?
Would you like a pamphlet?
You can sit over there. Enjoy the show.
Are you nervous?
Yeah.
Don't be nervous. You'll do great.
I can do this.
By the way, where's Kyungmin?
He's a bit late.
Right.
Is he getting ready in the next room?
We have a problem.
Kyungmin got hurt. He's in the hospital.
Huh?
Is it severe?
Not really.
But he probably needs further tests.
I don't think he'll make it
before the show starts.
It's him. See you later.
Why don't we cancel today's show...
How about you play Eden?
We can't just cancel the premiere.
You know all the lines and blocking.
You can do it.
No.
I can't act.
I'm here.
I really can't...
Go on stage with me.
You can do it.
I'm sick of this.
The same sea, the same routine.
I'm sick of this sea.
Every day is the same.
The waves are smiling,
but why am I stuck?
With every breath, my heart grows emptier,
as I'm trapped in this unknown place.
It's as if something is calling me.
That voice I thought I had long forgotten.
Even though I know it's out of reach,
once again,
I gaze toward you.
How is everyone doing?
Today,
I plan to go beyond that horizon.
I have a feeling
something interesting awaits me.
Eden, do you really not remember anything?
I don't think we've met before,
have we?
You promised me.
When we meet again,
you'd go see the sea with me.
I'm afraid you've got the wrong person.
The wrong person?
Then can you
hug me
for one last time?
Why did you just walk past me
as if we don't have a past?
Even if our eyes meet,
you just drift away.
Why do those looks I don't remember
still linger in my heart?
If this feeling is called love,
why does it come to me
in such a heartbreaking manner?
Don't talk about it in fleeting.
My heart somehow always lingers with you.
I only ask you to look at me once.
But one look might just shatter me.
Luka.
Open your eyes.
If the end of love is death,
that'd be too unfair.
Why did I only recover my memory now?
Why now,
at this moment?
I finally remembered your name,
but I could never call you again.
I fell in love
the moment I laid eyes on you.
[Eden: You saved me before.
Now it's my turn to save you.]
In front of everyone,
I want to confess to you.
I'll never let go of your hand.
I love you.
Go on.
Accept it.
You guys must've worried a lot about me.
Get well soon!
Argh!
Sorry.
You've to get well soon
and return to the stage!
I'm fine.
Don't worry.
We've concluded this show run.
How about dinner together to celebrate?
Uh, I think I'm developing a fatty liver.
My stomach doesn't feel good.
That's
your heart.
It's my sister's birthday.
I agreed to eat with my family.
I'll get going!
Me too. My stomach hurts.
I'll head out.
Well done with the show.
Didn't Kyungmin say he's an only child?
Yeah.
Seho's so bad at lying.
Those two...
Love is in the air. 100%.
We'll probably get very busy
once the national tour starts.
Yeah.
It'll be a whirlwind
for at least half a year.
Still... I'm excited.
After all, I'll be with you.
This is nice.
Ah! This is nice!
This time,
I won't let you go.
Is this not the right move?
I love you.
I love you more.